<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>BioThumos</title>
      <link>https://biothumos.github.io</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on BioThumos</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Cell Danger Response (CDR)</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/cdr</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/cdr</guid>
    <description>ME/CFS, CDR, and Treatments — crisp notes Conceptual model Illness sustained by a chronic Cell Danger Response (CDR) with immune exhaustion, mitochondrial dysfunction, limbic sensitization, and persistent alarmins.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>ME/CFS Treatment Protocol - v0.1</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Chronic-illness/mecfs-treatment-protocol</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Chronic-illness/mecfs-treatment-protocol</guid>
    <description> see testing and chronic-pathogen-testing to determine phenotype and areas of interest TODO: immunopeptidome changing to fix HLA mismatch itaconate shunt innate opiod receptor tolerance → bacopa → then methylene blue fosmanogepix for fungal stuff Basics: use in all stages ARA-290 → fix SFN takes a l...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Longevity Protocol - v0.1</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Longevity/longevity-protocol</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Longevity/longevity-protocol</guid>
    <description>TODO: gut health, probiotics bone health: L.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Conversations Excerpts: A.S.</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/_priv-conv-as</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/_priv-conv-as</guid>
    <description>analyisis of my immune status: I am not usually a massive fan of Dr Patterson’s cytokine panels, but I really like this particular result Immune activation is weighted towards Th2 (IL-4, IL-13), which neatly explains MCAS - Th2 T cells encourage humoral immunity via B cell stimulation → IgE I consid...</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Conversation Excerpts: D.C.</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/_priv-conv-dc</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/_priv-conv-dc</guid>
    <description>Viral driver of ME (WTHHF) In us humans it’s almost impossible with the approved antivirals to remove viral infections like EBV, CMV, HHV6 from the central nervous system.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Conversation Excerpts: S.</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/conv-s</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/conv-s</guid>
    <description>Ablify If it’s Abilify, I just wanted to let you know that I have a friend who has remained mostly asymptomatic thanks to Abilify.</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>GI Health</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/gut</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/gut</guid>
    <description>David Kaufman &amp; Ilene Ruhoy www.youtube.com/watch Ruhoy likes enteragem: expensive, 1-3 months should be enough, reduces gut inflammation cheaper versions: SBI protect, IG spore, glutashield enteragem is more potent though sx treatment, not core SIBO treatments (Kaufman): getting rid of inapprop...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Chronic Lyme (notes)</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/chronic-lyme</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Notes/chronic-lyme</guid>
    <description>Tania Dempsey &amp; David Kaufman www.youtube.com/watch David Kaufman Testing www.youtube.com/watch thinks all 3 B’s have herpes-like latent/reactivation dynamics based on his experience doesn’t pursue serology testing for this reason if we accept it’s a reactivating disease, antibody testing is les...</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Whole Genome Sequencing</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/wgs</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/wgs</guid>
    <description> I advise against the trendy online direct-to-customer labs due to many issues (see below) and instead recommend finding a non-trendy local accredited lab that has thorough documentation on their processes and technology (or is willing to tell you in detail).</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Chronic Pathogen Testing</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/chronic-pathogen-testing</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/chronic-pathogen-testing</guid>
    <description> most of these pathogens are hard to detect in their chronic stage IgM won’t be positive for most chronic cases 16x the IgG negative range upper-bound should be considered active there is no single test that can prove chronic infection, instead you need: a combination of different tests periodic re-...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>