<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>BioThumos</title>
      <link>https://biothumos.github.io</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on BioThumos</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Whole Genome Sequencing</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/WGS</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/WGS</guid>
    <description> I advise against the trendy online direct-to-customer labs due to many issues (see below) and instead recommend finding a non-trendy local accredited lab that has thorough documentation on their processes and technology (or is willing to tell you in detail).</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Chronic Pathogen Testing</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/chronic-pathogen-testing</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Testing/chronic-pathogen-testing</guid>
    <description> most of these pathogens are hard to detect in their chronic stage IgM won’t be positive for most chronic cases 16x the IgG negative range upper-bound should be considered active there is no single test that can prove chronic infection, instead you need: a combination of different tests periodic re-...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The BioThumos Knowledge Base</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/</guid>
    <description>This is a collection of knowledge on COVID, Long COVID, ME/CFS, health optimization, longevity, and other related topics based on latest research and anecdotes.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 12:13:08 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Peptide Guide - v1.0</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/Peptide/guide</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/Peptide/guide</guid>
    <description>Knowledge based on the experience of friends far more knowledgeable than me, as well as my own attempts and many hours of research, containing hard-to-find information from esoteric internet forums.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Long COVID Prevention Protocol - v1.2</title>
    <link>https://biothumos.github.io/ME--and--Long-COVID/covid-protocol</link>
    <guid>https://biothumos.github.io/ME--and--Long-COVID/covid-protocol</guid>
    <description>Will keep up to date. Only established advice is included here. If you know me, ask for prescription-free sources I can’t list publicly.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>